Curriculum Vitae Farhang Hassan Wazeer

Farhang Hassan Wazeer

Manager, former accountant & team leader

Address: Al-Askary quarter, Duhok - Iraq Tel: 0750 866 6676 / 0750 409 7162

Email: <u>farhng07@gmail.com</u>
Date of birth: 1st February 1987

Nationality: Iraq Gender: Male

Highly professional and experienced manager and accountant with over tw13 years progressively responsible experience managing responsibilities of one of the largest flour factory in North of Iraq. Demonstrated proficiency in leading large number of people, coordinating sales and distribution operations, and liaising with professionals of all levels; coupled with strong ability to assess services and support, High knowledge of budgeting and accounting, with profound experience and skilled in planning, economic development, and personnel management, Able to communicate in Kurdish, Arabic and English

WORK HISTORY

Feb2018–Present NEW DERIN GROUP SECURITY COMPANY Job title: Security supervisor & team leader

Erbil, Iraq

- Security supervisor & team leader
- Taking over the responsibility of supervising and managing 35 security officers.
- Securing one of the busiest shopping areas in Erbil (Langa), preventing violence aggressions
- Distribute the work among the team in to three shifts, 8am-4pm, 4pm-12am, and 12am-8am.
- Prepare and organize a working schedule for every shift, direct the staff to their roles.
- Arrange and conduct team meetings on weekly basis, give more instructions, highlight the main issues and concerns, actions and outcomes. And attends the company meetings.
- Organize & arrange training courses for the staff, insuring their skills always up to date.
- Responsible for obtaining and providing them with all necessary equipment, security wears.
- Using real weapons, electricity bar, helmet, gloves, shoes are all designed for these purposes.
- Making reports to the company stating the activities, cases of violence and actions taken.
- Making sure all the staff are following the company codes of conduct and principles reacting to people and while making action during their duty.
- Making sure all staff are following the principles of confidentiality of people & the company
- Coordinate the police, Erbil security department & crime prevention department.
- Daily reporting and correspondence with the company head office in Erbil.
- I would keep the files and documentations of each officer, monitor and evaluate their performance and make sure they compline with company principles and codes of conducts.

2009–2017 AKRE MAINFACTORY FOR FLOUR PRODUCTIONS Job title: General Manager

Akre district, Duhok, Iraq

- Taking over the managerial responsibilities given to me, reinstalling and setting up new production plan, enabled the factory to increase the production.
- Managing 36 workers and 46 drivers, responsible for their performance, payments, leaves, recruitment and ending services accordingly.
- The factory has the production capacity of up to 220-230 tons of flour per day.
- The manufacture is fully supplied with 16 machines, materials, and 8 production lines.
- Managing & supervising 2 engineers, 2 mechanics and 3 electrician engineers, accountants, and drivers.
- Carried out personally all needed coordination and liaising with the relevant authorities and government department, and other stockholders.
- The factory supply the majority of Iraq with good quality of flour, such as Erbil, Duhok, Zakho, Kirkuk, Suleimany, Najaf, Kerbala...Etc.
- Contracted with the ministry of General Trading of Iraq to supply the food rations agency with all the need of flour, which is distributed among the citizens of Iraq.

Curriculum Vitae Farhang Hassan Wazeer

- Ensuring the raw materials (mainly Wheat) that are used, confer to quality standards.
- Responsible for provide the safe environment for the production processes, making sure the employees are following the safety regulations during work.
- Prepared and made regular, monthly, quarterly and annual reports about the total and net revenues, incomes, expenditure, loses, concerns and actions to be taken.
- Report to the owners, calculating their revenues and profits according to their ownership rates.

2004–2009 AKRE MAINFACTORY FOR FLOUR PRODUCTIONS

Akre district, Duhok, Iraq

Job title: Accountant Manager

- Carried out all financial duties, such as paying salaries of 36 employees and 46 drivers.
- Responsible for checking and calculating the amount of wheat we have received and coordinate with suppliers regarding their payments.
- Effectively manage the cash flow, prepared monthly finance analysis, forecast budgets and financial statement preparation.
- Responsible for conducting regular follow ups and calculations of the finance outcomes of the factory, recording incomes, expenditure, daily costs, loses...etc.
- Handling more than IQD280,000,000–300,000,000 equivalent to (\$240,000) every month.
- Carried out monthly finance & stock checking, items, raw materials in the warehouses, equipment, vehicles, machines, incomes, expenditures, payments, depts., & send the report to the management.
- Report to the owners, calculating their revenues and profits according to their ownership rates.

EDUCATION

2012

THE INSTITUTE OF LAW ADMINISTRATION

Akre, Duhok, Iraq

High Diploma degree in law administration

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Good acknowledge & experience in use of computer, M. office, word, internet & emailing.
- Excellent organizing, administration and time management skills.
- Communication and building relationships, very diplomatic person
- Strong knowledge of customer services, and negotiations skills.
- High ability to maintain confidentiality and build customers' trust
- Excellent persuasive, communication and customer service skills
- Very flexible and ready to work in any shift, and on weekends and holidays
- Excellent time management, scheduling tasks and setting out goals.
- Highly skilled and experienced in the field of coordination and liaising with relevant people.
- In possession of valid Iraqi public driving license.

LANGUAGES

Languages	Understanding	Speaking	Writing	Reading	
Kurdish (Native)	Fluency	Fluency	Fluency	Fluency	
Arabic	Fluency	Fluency	Fluency	Fluency	
English	Under-Intermediate	Under-Interme	diate Under-Inte	rmediate Under-Intermediate	